<FTL>
<event name="FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT">
	<text>You arrive at the beacon to the sound of laser fire and explosions in the distance. A Duskbringer transport is engaged in a dogfight with a MV Rebel some distance away, both sides too engrossed in the conflict to notice your arrival. If you wanted, you could try and take on one of the vessels yourself, though there's no telling what sort of response you'll get from the other if you succeed.</text>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Help the Duskbringers.</text>
		<event>
			<text>Duskbringers may be extremists, but at least they're better than Rebels. You draw the MV Rebel's attention and prepare to engage with it.</text>
			<ship load="SHIP_FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_MV" hostile="true"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Help the MV Rebels.</text>
		<event>
			<text>The Rebels may be your enemies, but they surely can't be all bad, right? You open fire at the transport to draw its attention, which retaliates by boarding you with several Duskbringers!</text>
			<boarders min="3" max="3" class="zoltan_devotee"/>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<ship load="SHIP_FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_DUSK" hostile="true"/>
				<text>Continue...</text>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Try to talk them into standing down.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You steer your ship into the middle of the conflict and broadcast a simple request to stop fighting. Both captains pause and stare at you for a moment before resuming like nothing happened. Looks like diplomacy won't be an option here...</text>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Help the Duskbringers.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Duskbringers may be extremists, but at least they're better than Rebels. You draw the MV Rebel's attention and prepare to engage with it.</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_MV" hostile="true"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice hidden="true">
				<text>Help the MV Rebels.</text>
				<event>
					<text>The Rebels may be your enemies, but they surely can't be all bad, right? You open fire at the transport to draw its attention, which retaliates by boarding you with several Duskbringers!</text>
					<ship load="SHIP_FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_DUSK" hostile="true"/>
					<boarders min="3" max="3" class="zoltan_devotee"/>
					<choice hidden="true">
						<text>Continue...</text>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Leave before things get worse.</text>
				<event>
					<text>Given how poorly received your first attempt at negotiation was, you decide to head back before either ship decides to turn on you instead.</text>
					<choice>
						<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
						<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
					</choice>
					<choice>
						<text>Do nothing.</text>
						<event/>
					</choice>
				</event>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Stay uninvolved - this isn't your fight.</text>
		<event>
			<text>You don't fancy getting caught in the crossfire between two warring vessels both openly hostile to the Federation, so you steer far away from the conflict and find a nice quiet place to charge the FTL drive.</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
				<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
			</choice>
			<choice>
				<text>Do nothing.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<ship name="SHIP_FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_MV" auto_blueprint="LIST_SHIPS_MULTIVERSE">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The MV Rebel explodes into an assortment of scrap matter and other useful materials.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Check in with the Duskbringers.</text>
			<event load="FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_DUSK_CHECKIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>The MV Rebel's crew has been neutralized, leaving its ship a lifeless wreck. You collect all that you can find.</text>
		<autoReward level="HIGH">standard</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Check in with the Duskbringers.</text>
			<event load="FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_DUSK_CHECKIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>
<event name="FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_DUSK_CHECKIN">
	<text>The transport's captain hails you, their ship a little worse for wear but still in relatively good shape. "As much as I hate to admit it, your assistance was indeed timely. We were tasked with delivering military supplies to the Rebels, but I don't want anything to do with those bastards after this one ambushed us out of nowhere. Here, have some supplies - we won't be needing them anymore."</text>
	<autoreward level="MED">missiles</autoreward>
	<choice hidden="true">
		<text>Accept their gift and wish them on their way.</text>
		<event/>
	</choice>
	<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DUSK">
		<text>(Duskbringer Crew) Ask to buy a weapon.</text>
		<event>	
			<text>The captain mulls it over for a while before eventually agreeing to trade with you. "I suppose it's fine for you to buy a weapon, given that we're heading straight back to the Capitol after this."</text>
			<choice>
				<text>Buy a Loot Heavy Energy.</text>
				<item_modify>
					<item type="scrap" min="70" max="-60"/>
				</item_modify>
				<weapon name="LOOT_DUSKBRINGER_1"/>
			</choice>
			<!-- In event we have more loot duskbringer weapons will need to add more choices here -->
			<choice>
				<text>Respectfully decline.</text>
				<event/>
			</choice>
		</event>
	</choice>
</event>
<ship name="SHIP_FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_DUSK" auto_blueprint="MU_DUSK_TRANSPORT">
	<destroyed>
		<text>The Duskbringer transport explodes violently, whatever goods the ship contained having surely been destroyed in the process. However, you manage to salvage a good amount of scrap and functional ammunition from the wreckage.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">missiles</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Check in with the MV Rebels.</text>
			<event load="LIST_FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_MV_CHECKIN"/>
		</choice>
	</destroyed>
	<deadCrew>
		<text>The Duskbringer transport has been emptied of crew. Inside, you find some scrap and an Energy weapon, which you haul back to the ship in triumph.</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
		<weapon name="LIST_WEAPONS_ENERGY"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Check in with the Duskbringers.</text>
			<event load="LIST_FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_MV_CHECKIN"/>
		</choice>
	</deadCrew>
</ship>
<eventList name="LIST_FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_MV_CHECKIN">
	<event>
		<text>The MV Rebel hails you. "I don't know why on earth you decided to help us back there, and I frankly don't care. That said, I suppose I can feed the fleet false information as payback - beats spying on some random transport ship I guess." The MV Rebel jumps away.</text>
		<modifyPursuit amount="-2"/>
		<choice>
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The MV Rebel hails you, their captain's sunny disposition contrasting with the poor state of their ship's engines. "Thanks for the assist - those damn Duskbringers put up a pretty good fight for a 'supply vessel'. Now, I know we've got our differences and all, but I'm a diplomat, and I firmly believe that any disagreement can be solved with scrap. Have some, on the house."</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
		<choice>
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event>
		<text>The MV Rebel makes no attempt to hail you, jumping away in a puff of smoke a short while later. You feel a sense of dread as you realize your location might have been compromised, but at least you can salvage what little debris was left behind from the jump.</text>
		<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
		<autoReward level="LOW">fuel</autoReward>
		<choice>
			<text>Continue...</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
</eventList>
</FTL>