<FTL>
	<eventList name="ITEM_FRONTIER">
		<event load="FRONTIER_REBEL_ARGUMENT"/>
		<event load="FRONTIER_VETERAN_SURVEY"/>
	</eventList>

	<eventList name="NEUTRAL_FRONTIER">
		<event load="FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT"/>
		<event load="FRONTIER_ELITE_INSULT"/>
	</eventList>
	
	<eventList name="DISTRESS_FRONTIER">
		<event load="FRONTIER_FAKENEWS"/>

	</eventList>

	<event name="FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT" unique="true">
		<text>You arrive at the beacon to find a Duskbringer transport sparring with an MV Rebel some distance away. If you wanted, you could try and take on one of the vessels yourself, though there's no telling what response you'd receive from the other ship afterwards.</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Help the Duskbringers.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You draw the MV Rebel's attention and prepare to engage with it.</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_MV" hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Help the MV Rebels.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You open fire at the transport to draw its attention, which retaliates by boarding you with several Duskbringers!</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_DUSK" hostile="true"/>
				<boarders min="2" max="3" class="zoltan_devotee"/>
				<choice hidden="true">	
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Stay uninvolved - this isn't your fight.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You don't fancy getting caught in the crossfire between two warring vessels both openly hostile to the Federation. They'll sort it out eventually.</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
					<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>Do nothing.</text>
					<event/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event name="FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_DUSK">
		<text>The Duskbringer transport hails you, their ship a little worse for wear but still in relatively good shape. "As much as I hate to admit it, your assistance was indeed timely. We were tasked with delivering military supplies to the Rebels, but were surprised at the sheer hostility of those we considered our 'allies'. Here, have some supplies - we won't be needing them anymore."</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">missiles</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Accept their gift and wish them on their way.</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DUSK" blue="true">
			<text>(Duskbringer Crew) Ask to buy a weapon.</text>
			<event>	
				<text>The captain mulls it over for a while before eventually agreeing to trade with you. "I suppose it's fine for you to buy a weapon - we won't be needing them after this."</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Buy an Energy weapon.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-45" max="-55"/>
					</item_modify>
					<weapon name="GIFTLIST_ENERGY"/>
					<event/>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>Buy a Loot Weapon.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-60" max="-70"/>
					</item_modify>
					<weapon name="LIST_LOOT_DUSKBRINGER"/>
					<event/>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>Respectfully decline.</text>
					<event/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<eventList name="FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_MV">
		<event>
			<text>The MV Rebel hails you. "I don't know why on earth you decided to help us back there, and I frankly don't give a damn. That said, I suppose I can feed the fleet false information as payback - beats doing border patrol I guess." They jump away.</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="-2"/>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The MV Rebel hails you. "Thanks for the assist - those Duskbringers didn't know the meaning of 'import tax'. Now, I know we've got our differences and all, but I'm a businessman, and I firmly believe that any disagreement can be solved with scrap. Have some, on the house."</text>
			<autoReward level="LOW">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The MV Rebel makes no attempt to hail you, jumping away in a puff of smoke a short while later. You feel a sense of dread as you realize your location has likely been compromised, but at least you can salvage some debris left behind from the jump.</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
			<autoReward level="LOW">fuel</autoReward>
		</event>
	</eventList>
	
	<event name="FRONTIER_ELITE_INSULT" unique="true">
		<ship load="SHIP_FRONTIER_ELITE_INSULT" hostile="false"/>
		<text>The Elite Rebel at this beacon hails you as you jump in, seemingly anticipating your arrival. "So THIS is the Renegade command's been going crazy over? HA! Given the size of the bounty on your head, I'd have thought you'd be piloting something a bit bigger, not this tiny little shrimp!"</text> 
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>How dare you! Man the guns.</text>
			<event>
				<text>The Rebel captain smirks at you as their weapons system comes to life. "Prepare to be crushed, squirt."</text>
				<ship hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="WEAPON_PREIGNITE" blue="true">
			<!---  preigniting augments)-->
			<text>(Weapon Pre-igniter) Nuke them.</text>
			<event>
				<text>Without missing a beat, you fire a salvo directly into the Elite's shields, creating a massive explosion that sends a good chunk of their ship flying into space. The captain hastily apologizes and ejects a weapon out the airlock as surrender before running as far away from your ship as physically possible.</text>
				<enemyDamage amount="6" system="engines" effect="breach" force="true" damageHull="true"/>
				<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
				<weapon name="GIFTLIST_REBEL"/>
				<instantEscape/>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_INSTANT_DAMAGE" blue="true">
			<!--- list of damaging pre-emptive weapons)-->
			<text>(Damaging Pre-Emptive Weapon) Shoot them while they're exposed.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You fire your pre-emptive weapon directly into the Elite's weapons system, ripping a hole into it. The captain's haughty disposition fades as they realize your ship is no small threat. "Alright alright, you've made your point already! Would a weapon suffice to leave us alone?"</text>
				<enemyDamage amount="3" system="weapons" effect="breach" force="true" damageHull="true"/>
				<choice>
					<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
					<event>
						<autoReward level="LOW">weapon</autoReward>
					</event>
				</choice>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Nah, we'll just murder you anyways.</text>
					<event>
						<text>The captain steels their resolve and prepares to face you in combat.</text>
						<ship hostile="true"/>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Continue...</text>
							<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_INSTANT_NODAMAGE" blue="true">
			<!--- list of non-damaging pre-emptive weapons)-->
			<text>(Non-Damaging Pre-Emptive Weapon) Shoot them while they're exposed.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You fire your pre-emptive weapon directly into the Elite's weapons system, crippling it and lighting it ablaze. The captain's haughty disposition fades as they realize your ship is no small threat. "Alright alright, you've made your point already! Would a weapon suffice to leave us alone?"</text>
				<status type="loss" target="enemy" amount="1" system="weapons"/>
				<enemyDamage amount="0" system="weapons" effect="fire"/>			
				<choice>
					<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
					<event>
						<autoReward level="LOW">weapon</autoReward>
					</event>
				</choice>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Nah, we'll just murder you anyways.</text>
					<event>
						<text>The captain steels their resolve and prepares to face you in combat.</text>
						<ship hostile="true"/>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Continue...</text>
							<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="weapons" lvl="6" blue="true">
			<text>(Lvl 6 Weapons) Show the Elite you mean business.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You fire your entire salvo of weaponry at the Rebel vessel, narrowly missing it and vaporizing a nearby asteroid instead. The captain looks impressed, despite their best efforts to hide it. "Heh, nice laser light show you got over there. Listen - maybe we don't have to fight after all? It's not like I'm scared or anything - I just don't want to ruin the paint job."</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
					<event>
						<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
					</event>
				</choice>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Reject the offer and begin combat.</text>
					<event>
						<ship hostile="true"/>
						<text>"Your loss. I'll still win anyways." The Elite cuts comms and begins offensive mauevers.</text>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Continue...</text>
							<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="artillery" lvl="4" blue="true">
			<text>(Lvl 4 Artillery) Show the Elite you mean business.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You fire your artillery at the Rebel vessel, narrowly missing it and vaporizing a nearby asteroid instead. The captain looks impressed, despite their best efforts to hide it. "Heh, nice laser light show you got over there. Listen... maybe we don't have to fight after all? It's not like I'm scared or anything - I just don't want to ruin the paint job."</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
					<event>
						<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
					</event>
				</choice>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Reject the offer and begin combat.</text>
					<event>
						<ship hostile="true"/>
						<text>"Your loss. I'll still win anyways." The Elite cuts comms and begins offensive mauevers.</text>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Continue...</text>
							<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_JERRY" blue="true">
			<text>(Jerry) "Hello!"</text>
			<event>
				<text>Upon hearing Jerry speak, the captain's disposition changes to one of surprise and adoration. "Wait.. you have JERRY on your ship? I take everything back - I'm a huge fan!"
				
				After getting a signed photo of 'Jerome Wentworth himself', the Elite gives you a weapon and some scrap before heading out.</text>
				<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Just grab some earplugs and wait until he gives up.</text>
			<event>
				<text>After rambling at you for several minutes, the Elite realizes you aren't listening anymore, throws some curse words at you, and hangs up.</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
					<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>Do nothing.</text>
					<event/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
	
	<event name="FRONTIER_REBEL_ARGUMENT" unique="true">
		<text>Immediately upon jumping into the beacon, your comms light up with an argument being held over an open channel. After a brief search, you find the source to be three Rebel ships parked in a circle: A local Rebel Elite, an Engineer, and an MV Rebel.</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Tune in.</text>
			<event>
				<text>From what you can gather between the expletives, slurs, and ad hominem statements about certain parties' mothers, the three ships appear to be locked in a heated debate about which corps is the most vital to the Rebellion.
				
				"The Rebellion was built on the backs of us Elites! We're the ones who lead the charge, who make up almost the entirety of the Rebel Fleet to begin with! If it weren't for us, the Rebellion would've lost aeons ago!"
				
				"That was back then. This is now! The Multiverse is wide open, and we're the ones to explore it. There wouldn't even be a Rebellion in this shithole universe if we hadn't come through!"
				
				"Oh really? There wouldn't be a Rebellion. Great claim. One small issue, buddy. Check the fifteen thousand carriers' worth of Rebel Auto Ships scattered across the galaxy, waging our war for us without us even needing to lift a finger! The only reason there's even a Rebellion today is because of our damn work! Now admit it before I– Wait, is that a Fed?"
				
				All three ships turn to face you, weapons thrumming but not firing.</text>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Take no chances - attack them.</text>
					<event>
						<text>For a group supposedly divided, the three ships are surprisingly quick to unite in the face of danger. The Elite Rebel charges forward to engage with you while the Engineer and MV Rebel provide fire support from the sidelines!</text>
						<ship load="SHIP_FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_ELITE" hostile="true"/>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Continue...</text>
							<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Hold off - something's up.</text>
					<event load="FRONTIER_REBEL_ARGUMENT_2"/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>That's three ships too many. Let's leave.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You quickly turn around and leave the three ships to their squabbling. They don't seem to notice you.</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
					<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>Do nothing.</text>
					<event/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event name="FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE">
		<loadEventList seeded="false">
			<event name="FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE_DRONE" req="MARKER_FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE" lvl="0">
				<superDrones player="false" name="DRONE_SURGE_SMALL"/>
				<hiddenAug>MARKER_FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE</hiddenAug>
			</event>
			<event name="FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE_LASER" req="MARKER_FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE">
				<superBarrage player="false" name="LASER_SURGE_SMALL"/>
				<removeItem>HIDDEN MARKER_FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE</removeItem>
			</event>
		</loadEventList>
	</event>
	
	<event name="FRONTIER_REBEL_ARGUMENT_2">
		<text>After a moment of tense silence, the Engineer speaks up. "Hey, wait a second. If you're a Fed, that means you've probably fought some Rebels before, right? Maybe you can help us settle our little dilemma." 
			
		The MV Rebel bristles at the proposition. "They're not just Federation, numbnuts. They're a Renegade! Probably the same one the Fleet's after, if I had to guess."
			
		"Oh, so they've totally fought a bunch of us!" Chimes in the Elite.	
		
		"Ugh, that's - That's actually a good point."
		
		The three ships power their weapons down. 
			
		"So, Feddy boy. Which of us do you think is the most important to the Rebellion?"</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>The Rebel Elites.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You can't deny - The Elites certainly seem to handle most of the Rebellion's groundwork these days. 
					
				"Ha! Told you!" The Elite gloats, his words barely audible above his allies' collective groans. The other two ships quickly jump away, leaving you alone with the Elite.
					
				Thanks for that, man. Sometimes it feels like all the effort I've put into helping the Rebellion is just going to waste with guys like that. Actually, you know what? Screw 'em. I'm going with you guys."</text>
				<crewMember amount="1" class="human_soldier"/>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>The Multiversal Fleet.</text>
			<event>
				<text>The Rebellion probably wouldn't still be staying afloat without the extra manpower from U1, and U1 certainly wouldn't have much reach without the MV Fleet. The captain of the MV Vessel jeers triumphantly as the other two ships jump away in shame.
				
				"I never would've thought a Renegade of all people would back me up, but I guess this Multiverse is full of surprises, right? Here, take this weapon. From one Multiverse traveler to another."
				
				With that, he jumps away, leaving you with your spoils.</text>
				<weapon name="GIFTLIST_REBEL"/>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>The Engineer Corps.</text>
			<event>
				<text>While the Engineers may not be the most numerous or most active group in the Rebellion, you can't deny the sheer number of Auto Ships you've seen on your travels. The Elite and the MV Rebel groan in unison as the Engineer breaks into a bout of nasal laughter. Before long, both losers exit the system, leaving you alone with the Engineer.
				
				"Hehehe, I knew it was a good idea to ask you! Here - a drone schematic for your trouble. And stay safe out there! Federation or not, I wouldn't want to see a fellow appreciator of technology get blown to bits." The engineer jumps away.</text>
				<drone name="GIFTLIST_COMBAT_DRONES"/>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="human_mfk" blue="true">
			<text>(MFK Ace) The MFK Aces.</text>
			<event>
				<text>All three captains open their mouths to shout at you in unison, but their words die in their throats as they see your MFK Ace glare at them. They offer a series of hurried apologies and some scrap, then leave without another word.</text>
				<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_LEGION" blue="true">
			<text>(Legionnaire Crew) The Legionnaires.</text>
			<event>
				<text>"What's a legionnaire? Never heard of them before." 
					
					"Top secret. That's all anyone's allowed to know before I have to... silence them."
					
					All three captains seem sufficiently intimidated by your Legionnaire's demeanor and thinly veiled threat. They apologize and offer a weapon as tribute, then leave without another word.</text>
				<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_JERRY" blue="true">
			<text>(Jerry) "All of you!"</text>
			<event>
				<text>"Does it really matter which group is 'the best'? Sure, we wouldn't have a Rebellion without the Elites. But the same could be said for the MV Rebels, or the Engineers for that matter! Each of you is vitally important towards keeping the Rebellion running smoothly, so I guess you're all winners in a sense."
				
				Jerry finishes his speech to applause from all three captains.
				
				"Well said. To think we wasted several system hours bickering when the answer to our problem was so simple after all..."
				
				Before jumping away, the three ships each give you a gift as thanks for helping resolve the conflict.</text>
				<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
				<weapon name="GIFTLIST_REBEL"/>
				<modifyPursuit amount="-1"/>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>

	<event name="FRONTIER_VETERAN_SURVEY" unique="true">
		<text>A lone Rebel vessel hails you as you jump in. A young Rebel officer appears onscreen, though the look in his eyes suggests he's seen more than his fair share of battles. "A Fed? Interesting. Question: What's your honest opinion on the Rebellion as it stands today?"</text>
		<ship load="LIST_SHIPS_REBEL_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>It's a band of oppressive pests that has no right to exist in this universe.</text>
			<event>
				<text>The Rebel sighs. "Can't say I expected much else from a Federation vessel. If you truly think of me as but a mere 'pest', then I suppose the only way this encounter can end is in conflict." His ship's weapons come to life; yours soon do the same.</text>
				<ship hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>It's a glorious cause that will bring order and stability to the Multiverse.</text>
			<event>
				<text>"Please. Do you really think I'm stupid enough to believe that's your honest answer? If you're willing to lie to my face in a survey, I see no need to prolong this conversation any further." He cuts comms.</text>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>It has potential, but was led astray and no longer represents the ideals it once stood for.</text>
			<event>
				<text>"Finally, someone who understands me!" The Rebel smiles before sighing despondently. "I joined the Rebellion because I wanted to make a change, to 'help those that can't help themselves'. Turns out it's far worse than the commercials make it out to be. Hostile workplace environment, constant infighting between the different corps, upper management touting an extremely racist agenda... you get the idea. I've got half a mind to quit and find work elsewhere, but I need the money to pay off my loans..."</text>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Why not join our ship? The pay's good, and we even get free healthcare insurance.</text>
					<event>
						<text>"Sure, I guess. At least I won't have to listen to my commander bark orders at me anymore."</text>
						<crewMember amount="1" class="human_soldier" all_skills="1">Myles</crewMember>
					</event>
				</choice>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Why not try and form a worker's union?</text>
					<event>
						<text>"That's an idea. Never thought I'd be taking advice from a Fed, but I guess it's worth a shot." The Rebel gives you some scrap as thanks.</text>
						<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice> 
	</event>

	<event name="FRONTIER_FAKENEWS" unique="true">
		<beaconType id="map_icon_fakenews" global="false">
			<color r="255" g="180" b="248" a="1"/>
			<unvisitedTooltip>A strange transmission is coming from this beacon.</unvisitedTooltip>
			<visitedTooltip>Explored location. Nothing left of interest.</visitedTooltip>
			<undiscoveredTooltip>An unvisited location.</undiscoveredTooltip>
		</beaconType> <!--Can replace wtih regular distress beacon if need be-->
		<text>Upon arrival, your comms are flooded with a garbled message spanning across all broadband channels. "Th-he Federation is a bunch of ***** idiots! Aliens have been scientifically proven to be worse than hu-hu-humans! Are YOU a ***** tired of all the ******* scum polluting our universe? Then join the Multiversal Corps and start slaughtering Zoltan children NOW! Call now at (***)..." 
			
			The transmission seems to be coming from the other side of the planet, all other signals completely drowned out by the noise. How strange...</text>
		<img planet="PLANET_POPULATED_4"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Follow the transmission.</text>
			<event>
				<text>After a while, you manage to locate the source of the strange transmission - a large Auto-Station orbiting a planet, accompanied by a single Engineer vessel some distance away. They hail you as you arrive.   
					
					"Look, I know our two factions aren't exactly on the friendliest of terms, but I think the two of us could reach a... 'mutually beneficial agreement'. This station was recently hijacked by some U1 blockheads to 'educate the populace'. It's been spewing propaganda and firing at anything that comes in range ever since. I can't shut it down without approaching it, so I'll need some help to fix or disable it."</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_FRONTIER_FAKENEWS" hostile="false"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Agree to help fix the Auto.</text>
					<event>
						<text>"Thanks. Just don't blow it up - my paycheck depends on this."</text>
						<choice hidden="true" req="ANTI_VIRUS" blue="true">
							<text>(Anti-Virus Module) Use your Anti-Virus module to purge the virus.</text>
							<event>
								<text>You fire up the Anti-Virus and are able to remotely counter the station's virus in no time at all. The Engineer thanks you and gives you a drone before leaving.</text>
								<autoReward level="HIGH">drone</autoReward>
							</event>	
						</choice>
						<choice hidden="true" req="hacking" lvl="3" blue="true">
							<text>(Adv. Hacking) Hack the station to purge the virus.</text>
							<event>
								<text>Your advanced hacking system easily bypasses the station's firewalls and swiftly purges the virus from its systems. The Engineer thanks you for your assistance and gives you a drone as payment.</text>
								<autoReward level="HIGH">drone</autoReward>
							</event>
						</choice>
						<choice hidden="true" req="hacking" lvl="2" max_lvl="2" blue="true">
							<text>(Upg. Hacking) Hack the station to purge the virus.</text>
							<event>
								<text>With some difficulty, you manage to bypass the station's firewalls and clear the virus from its systems. The Engineer thanks you for your assistance and delivers a drone schematic as payment.</text>
								<autoReward level="MED">drone</autoReward>
							</event>
							<event>
								<text>The station's security measures are significantly more robust than you anticipated, and it takes a while for you to break through and delete the virus. The Engineer still thanks you for your assistance and provides payment, though you suspect the fleet will have gained a large lead on you by now.</text>
								<autoReward level="MED">drone</autoReward>
								<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
							</event>
						</choice>
						<choice hidden="true" req="hacking" lvl="1" max_lvl="1" blue="true">
							<text>(Hacking) Hack the station to purge the virus.</text>
							<event>
								<text>The station's defenses are far too advanced for your weak hacking system, and you barely manage to breach a single firewall before the security system locks you out. The Engineer is somewhat disappointed, but gives you a small reward for trying anyways.</text>
								<autoReward level="LOW">standard</autoReward>
							</event>
						<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGINEER" blue="true">
							<text>(Engineer Crew) Have your Engineer purge the virus.</text>
							<event>
								<text>Your Engineer, no stranger to dealing with broken Auto-ships, reformats its hard drive and reinstalls its operating system to wipe all traces of the virus from its systems. The Engineer seems impressed and gives you a drone as payment for a job well done.</text>
								<autoReward level="MED">drone</autoReward>
							</event>
						</choice>
						<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_ENGI" blue="true">
							<text>(Engi Crew) Have your Engi try and disable the Auto.</text>
							<event>
								<text>Your Engi is still able to fix the bug in the Auto's targeting AI, allowing the Engineer to close in and finish the job. The Engineer thanks you for your assistance and delivers a drone schematic as payment.</text>
								<autoReward level="MED">drone</autoReward>
							</event>
						</choice>
						<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_LANIUS" blue="true">
							<text>(Lanius Crew) Your Lanius seems to have a solution.</text>
							<event>
								<text>Your Lanius ejects itself from the airlock, its lack of heat signatures rendering it invisible to the Auto's targeting sensors. Once there, it burrows into the hull and digests the offending terminal. Though it certainly isn't the most elegant approach, a job is a job and the Engineer delivers payment nonetheless.</text>
								<autoReward level="LOW">drone</autoReward>
							</event>
						</choice>
						<choice hidden="true" req="COMBAT_WEAPONS_JAMMER" blue="true">
							<text>(Targeting Jammer) Jam the station's weapons to let the Engineer approach safely.</text>
							<event>
								<text>You fire up the targeting jammer and disable the Auto's weapons to let the Engineer close in and shut it down. The Engineer thanks you and delivers payment.</text>
								<autoReward level="LOW">drone</autoReward>
							</event>
						</choice>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Apologize and say there's nothing you can do.</text>
							<event>
								<text>You apologize and end comms.</text>
								<choice>
									<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
									<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
								</choice>
								<choice>
									<text>Do nothing.</text>
									<event/>
								</choice>
							</event>
						</choice>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Just blow it up.</text>
							<event>
								<text>You approach the station with weapons raised, their weapons rising in response to your approach.</text>
								<ship hostile="true"/>
								<choice hidden="true">
									<text>Continue...</text>
									<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
								</choice>
							</event>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>Decline.</text>
					<event>
						<text>You aren't going to do some Engineer's laundry work for them. You end the call and steer away from the malfunctioning Auto.</text>
						<choice>
							<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
							<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
						</choice>
						<choice>
							<text>Do nothing.</text>
							<event/>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice>
			<text>Ignore it and carry on.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You can't afford to go on a wild goose chase for every unknown signal you find.</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
					<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>Do nothing.</text>
					<event/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>

</FTL>