<FTL>
	<eventList name="ITEM_FRONTIER">
		<event load="FRONTIER_REBEL_ARGUMENT"/>
		<event load="FRONTIER_VETERAN_SURVEY"/>
	</eventList>

	<eventList name="NEUTRAL_FRONTIER">
		<event load="FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT"/>
		<event load="FRONTIER_ELITE_INSULT"/>
	</eventList>

	<event name="FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT" unique="true">
		<text>You arrive at the beacon to find a Duskbringer transport sparring with an MV Rebel some distance away. If you wanted, you could try and take on one of the vessels yourself, though there's no telling what response you'd receive from the other ship afterwards.</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Help the Duskbringers.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You draw the MV Rebel's attention and prepare to engage with it.</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_MV" hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Help the MV Rebels.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You open fire at the transport to draw its attention, which retaliates by boarding you with several Duskbringers!</text>
				<ship load="SHIP_FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_DUSK" hostile="true"/>
				<boarders min="2" max="3" class="zoltan_devotee"/>
				<choice hidden="true">	
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Stay uninvolved - this isn't your fight.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You don't fancy getting caught in the crossfire between two warring vessels both openly hostile to the Federation, so you steer far away from the conflict and find a nice quiet place to charge the FTL drive.</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
					<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>Do nothing.</text>
					<event/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event name="FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_DUSK_CHECKIN">
		<text>The Duskbringer transport hails you, their ship a little worse for wear but still in relatively good shape. "As much as I hate to admit it, your assistance was indeed timely. We were tasked with delivering military supplies to the Rebels, but even I was surprised at the sheer hostility of those blue bastards. Here, have some supplies - we won't be needing them anymore."</text>
		<autoReward level="MED">missiles</autoReward>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Accept their gift and wish them on their way.</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_DUSK" blue="true">
			<text>(Duskbringer Crew) Ask to buy a weapon.</text>
			<event>	
				<text>The captain mulls it over for a while before eventually agreeing to trade with you. "I suppose it's fine for you to buy a weapon, given that we're heading straight back to the Capitol after this."</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Buy a normal Energy weapon.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-45" max="-55"/>
					</item_modify>
					<weapon name="GIFTLIST_ENERGY"/>
					<event/>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>Buy a Loot Weapon.</text>
					<item_modify>
						<item type="scrap" min="-60" max="-70"/>
					</item_modify>
					<weapon name="LIST_LOOT_DUSKBRINGER"/>
					<event/>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>Respectfully decline.</text>
					<event/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<eventList name="FRONTIER_DOGFIGHT_MV_CHECKIN">
		<event>
			<text>The MV Rebel hails you. "I don't know why on earth you decided to help us back there, and I frankly don't give a damn. That said, I suppose I can feed the fleet false information as payback - beats doing border patrol I guess." They jump away.</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="-2"/>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The MV Rebel hails you. "Thanks for the assist - those Duskbringers didn't know the meaning of 'supply blockade'. Now, I know we've got our differences and all, but I'm a businessman, and I firmly believe that any disagreement can be solved with scrap. Have some, on the house."</text>
			<autoReward level="MED">scrap_only</autoReward>
		</event>
		<event>
			<text>The MV Rebel makes no attempt to hail you, jumping away in a puff of smoke a short while later. You feel a sense of dread as you realize your location has likely been compromised, but at least you can salvage some debris left behind from the jump.</text>
			<modifyPursuit amount="1"/>
			<autoReward level="LOW">fuel</autoReward>
		</event>
	</eventList>
	
	<event name="FRONTIER_ELITE_INSULT" unique="true">
		<ship load="SHIP_FRONTIER_ELITE_INSULT" hostile="false"/>
		<text>The Elite Rebel at this beacon hails you as you jump in, seemingly anticipating your arrival. "So THIS is the Renegade Command's been going crazy over? HA! Given the size of the bounty on your head, I'd have thought you'd be piloting something a bit bigger, not this tiny little shrimp! Get dunked on nerd!"</text> 
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>How dare you! Man the guns.</text>
			<event>
				<text>The Rebel captain smirks at you, their weapons system coming to life with an audible hum. "Ah Renegades, foolhardy as always. Prepare to be crushed, squirt."</text>
				<ship hostile="true"/>
				<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="WEAPON_PREIGNITE" blue="true">
			<!---  preigniting augments)-->
			<text>(Weapon Pre-igniter) Nuke them.</text>
			<event>
				<text>Without missing a beat, you fire a salvo directly into the Elite's shields, creating a massive explosion that sends a good chunk of their ship flying into space. The captain hastily apologizes and ejects a weapon out the airlock as surrender before running as far away from your ship as physically possible.</text>
				<enemyDamage amount="6" system="engines" effect="breach" force="true" damageHull="true"/>
				<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
				<weapon name="GIFTLIST_REBEL"/>
				<instantEscape/>
				<event/>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_INSTANT_DAMAGE" blue="true">
			<!--- list of damaging pre-emptive weapons)-->
			<text>(Damaging Pre-Emptive Weapon) Shoot them while they're exposed.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You fire your pre-emptive weapon directly into the Elite's weapons system, ripping a hole into it. The captain's haughty disposition fades as they realize your ship is no small threat. "Alright alright, you've made your point already! Would a weapon suffice to leave us alone?"</text>
				<enemyDamage amount="3" system="weapons" effect="breach" force="true" damageHull="true"/>
				<choice>
					<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
					<autoReward level="LOW">weapon</autoReward>
					<event/>
				</choice>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Nah, we'll just murder you anyways.</text>
					<event>
						<text>The captain steels their resolve and prepares to face you in combat.</text>
						<ship hostile="true"/>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Continue...</text>
							<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="BLUELIST_INSTANT_NODAMAGE" blue="true">
			<!--- list of non-damaging pre-emptive weapons)-->
			<text>(Non-Damaging Pre-Emptive Weapon) Shoot them while they're exposed.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You fire your pre-emptive weapon directly into the Elite's weapons system, crippling it and lighting it ablaze. The captain's haughty disposition fades as they realize your ship is no small threat. "Alright alright, you've made your point already! Would a weapon suffice to leave us alone?"</text>
				<status type="loss" target="enemy" amount="1" system="weapons"/>
				<enemyDamage amount="0" system="weapons" effect="fire"/>			
				<choice>
					<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
					<autoReward level="LOW">weapon</autoReward>
					<event/>
				</choice>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Nah, we'll just murder you anyways.</text>
					<event>
						<text>The captain steels their resolve and prepares to face you in combat.</text>
						<ship hostile="true"/>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Continue...</text>
							<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="weapons" lvl="6" blue="true">
			<text>(Lvl 6 Weapons) Show the Elite you mean business.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You fire your entire salvo of weaponry at the Rebel vessel, narrowly missing it and vaporizing a nearby asteroid instead. The captain looks impressed, despite their best efforts to hide it. "Heh, nice laser light show you got over there. Listen - maybe we don't have to fight after all? It's not like I'm scared or anything - I just don't want to ruin the paint job."</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Sure, I guess.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
					<event/>
				</choice>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Reject the offer and begin combat.</text>
					<event>
						<ship hostile="true"/>
						<text>"Your loss. I'll still win anyways." The Elite cuts comms and begins offensive mauevers.</text>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Continue...</text>
							<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="artillery" lvl="4" blue="true">
			<text>(Lvl 4 Artillery) Show the Elite you mean business.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You fire your artillery at the Rebel vessel, narrowly missing it and vaporizing a nearby asteroid instead. The captain looks impressed, despite their best efforts to hide it. "Heh, nice laser light show you got over there. Listen... maybe we don't have to fight after all? It's not like I'm scared or anything - I just don't want to ruin the paint job."</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Sure, I guess.</text>
					<autoReward level="HIGH">standard_no_item</autoReward>
					<event/>
				</choice>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Reject the offer and begin combat.</text>
					<event>
						<ship hostile="true"/>
						<text>"Your loss. I'll still win anyways." The Elite cuts comms and begins offensive mauevers.</text>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Continue...</text>
							<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
						</choice>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_JERRY" blue="true">
			<text>(Jerry) "Hello!"</text>
			<event>
				<text>Upon hearing Jerry speak, the captain's disposition changes to one of surprise and adoration. "Wait.. you have JERRY on your ship? I take everything back - I'm a huge fan!"
				
				After getting a signed photo of Jerome Wentworth himself, the Elite gives you a weapon and some scrap before heading out.</text>
				<autoReward level="HIGH">weapon</autoReward>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Just grab some earplugs and hope he gives up.</text>
			<event>
				<text>After rambling at you for several minutes, the Elite realizes you aren't listening anymore, throws some curse words at you, and hangs up.</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
					<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>Do nothing.</text>
					<event/>
				</choice>
			</event>
			<event>
				<text>"Hey bozo! You deaf or something? "</text>
				<ship hostile="true"/>
				<choice>
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event name="SURRENDER_FRONTIER_ELITE_INSULT">
		<text>You receive a hail from the Elite's captain, having clearly undererestimated your ship's strength. "Alright alright, you've made your point already! Just take this weapon and leave us alone!"</text>
		<choice>
			<text>Accept their surrender.</text>
			<weapon name="GIFTLIST_REBEL"/>
			<ship hostile="false"/>
		</choice>
		<choice>
			<text>Ignore them and continue fighting.</text>
			<event/>
		</choice>
	</event>
	
	<event name="FRONTIER_REBEL_ARGUMENT" unique="true">
		<text>Immediately upon jumping into the beacon, your comms light up with an argument being held over an open channel. After a brief search, you find the source to be three Rebel ships parked in a circle: A local Rebel Elite, an Engineer, and an MV Rebel.</text>
		<choice>
			<text>Tune in.</text>
			<event>
				<text>From what you can gather between the expletives, slurs, and ad hominem statements about certain parties' mothers, the three ships appear to be locked in a heated debate about which corps is the most vital to the Rebellion.</text>
				
				"The Rebellion was built on the backs of us Elites! We're the ones who lead the charge, who make up almost the entirety of the Rebel Fleet to begin with! If it weren't for us, the Rebellion would've lost aeons ago!"
				
				"That was back then. This is now! The Multiverse is wide open, and we're the ones to explore it. There wouldn't even be a Rebellion in this shithole universe if we hadn't come through!"
				
				"Oh really? There wouldn't be a Rebellion. Great claim. One small issue, buddy. Check the fifteen thousand carriers' worth of Rebel Auto Ships scattered across the galaxy, waging our war for us without us even needing to lift a finger! The only reason there's even a Rebellion today is because of our damn work! Now admit it before I– Wait, is that a Fed?"
				
				All three ships turn to face you, weapons thrumming but not firing.</text>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Take no chances - attack them.</text>
					<event>
						<text>For a group supposedly divided, the three ships are suprisingly quick to unite in the face of danger. The Elite Rebel charges forward to engage with you while the Engineer and MV Rebel provide fire support from the sidelines!</text>
						<ship name="SHIP_FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_ELITE" hostile="true"/>
						<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
					</event>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Hold off - something's up.</text>
					<event load="FRONTIER_REBEL_ARGUMENT_2"/>
				</choice>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>That's three ships too many. Let's leave.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You quickly turn around and leave the three ships to their squabbling. They don't seem to notice you.</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Do something onboard the ship.</text>
					<event load="STORAGE_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>Do nothing.</text>
					<event/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
	<event name="FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE">
		<loadEventList seeded="false">
			<event name="FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE_DRONE" req="MARKER_FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE" lvl="0">
				<superDrones player="false" name="DRONE_SURGE_SMALL"/>
				<hiddenAug>MARKER_FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE</hiddenAug>
			</event>
			<event name="FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE_LASER" req="MARKER_FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE">
				<superBarrage player="false" name="LASER_SURGE_SMALL"/>
				<removeItem>HIDDEN MARKER_FRONTIER_ARGUMENT_SURGE</removeItem>
			</event>
		</loadEventList>
	</event>
	<surgeDrones name="DRONE_SURGE_BASIC">
		<drone name="COMBAT_1_LASER" count="1"/>
		<drone name="FLAK_1_AMP3" count="1"/>
		<drone name="COMBAT_1_BEAM" count="1"/>
	</surgeDrones>
	<surgeBarrage name="LASER_SURGE_BASIC">
		<weapon name="BARRAGE_LASER" count="3"/>
	</surgeBarrage>
	<event name="FRONTIER_REBEL_ARGUMENT_2">
		<text>After a moment of tense silence, the Engineer speaks up. "Hey, wait a second. If you're a Fed, that means you've probably fought some Rebels before, right? Maybe you can help us settle our little dilemma." 
			
		The MV Rebel bristles at the proposition. "They're not just Federation, numbnuts. They're a Renegade! Probably the same one the Fleet's after, if I had to guess."
			
		"Oh, so they've totally fought a bunch of us!" Chimes in the Elite.	
		
		"Ugh, that's - That's actually a good point."
		
		The three ships power their weapons down. 
			
		"So, Feddy boy. Which of us do you think is the most important to the Rebellion?"</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>The Rebel Elites.</text>
			<event>
				<text>You can't deny - The Elites certainly seem to handle most of the Rebellion's groundwork these days. 
					
				"Ha! Told you!" The Elite gloats, his words barely audible above his allies' collective groans. The other two ships quickly jump away, leaving you alone with the Elite.
					
				Thanks for that, man. Sometimes it feels like all the effort I've put into helping the Rebellion is just going to waste with guys like that. Actually, you know what? Screw 'em. I'm going with you guys."</text>
				<crewMember amount="1" class="human_soldier">MacDonald</crewMember>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>The Multiversal Fleet.</text>
			<event>
				<text>The Rebellion probably wouldn't still be staying afloat without the extra manpower from U1, and U1 certainly wouldn't have much reach without the MV Fleet. The captain of the MV Vessel jeers triumphantly as the other two ships jump away in shame.
				
				"I never would've thought a Renegade of all people would back me up, but I guess this Multiverse is full of surprises, right? Here, take this weapon. From one Multiverse traveler to another."
				
				With that, he jumps away, leaving you with your spoils.</text>
				<weapon name="GIFTLIST_REBEL"/>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>The Engineer Corps.</text>
			<event>
				<text>While the Engineers may not be the most numerous or most active group in the Rebellion, you can't deny the sheer number of Auto Ships you've seen on your travels. The Elite and the MV Rebel groan in unison as the Engineer breaks into a bout of nasal laughter. Before long, both losers exit the system, leaving you alone with the Engineer.
				
				"Hehehe, I knew it was a good idea to ask you! Here - a drone schematic for your trouble. And stay safe out there! Federation or not, I wouldn't want to see a fellow appreciator of technology get blown to bits." The engineer jumps away.</text>
				<drone name="GIFTLIST_COMBAT_DRONES"/>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="human_mfk" blue="true">
			<text>(MFK Ace) The MFK Aces.</text>
			<event>
				<text>All three captains open their mouths to shout at you in unison, but their words die in their throats as they see your MFK Ace glare at them. They offer a series of hurried apologies and some scrap, then leave without another word.</text>
				<autoReward level="HIGH">scrap_only</autoReward>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true" req="LIST_CREW_JERRY" blue="true">
			<text>(Jerry) "All of you!"</text>
			<event>
				<text>"Does it really matter which group is 'the best'? Sure, we wouldn't have a Rebellion without the Elites. But the same could be said for the MV Rebels, or the Engineers for that matter! Each of you is vitally important towards keeping the Rebellion running smoothly, so I guess you're all winners in a sense."
				
				Jerry finishes his speech to applause from all three captains.
				
				"Well said. To think we wasted several system hours bickering when the answer to our problem was so simple after all..."
				
				"Guys, I'm sorry for being a bit stubborn and saying things about your mothers."
				
				"It's fine."
				
				"Apology accepted."
				
				Before jumping away, the three ships each give you a gift as thanks for helping resolve the conflict.</text>
				<autoReward level="MED">scrap-only</autoReward>
				<weapon name="GIFTLIST_REBEL"/>
				<modifyPursuit amount="-1"/>
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>

	<event name="FRONTIER_VETERAN_SURVEY" unique="true">
		<text>A lone Rebel vessel hails you as you jump in. A young Rebel officer appears onscreen, though the look in his eyes suggests he's seen more than his fair share of battles. "A Fed? Interesting. Question: What's your honest opinion on the Rebellion as it stands today?"</text>
		<ship name="LIST_SHIPS_REBEL_FIGHT" hostile="false"/>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>It's a band of oppressive, stupid pests that has no right to exist in this universe.</text>
			<event>
				<text>The Rebel sighs. "Can't say I expected much else from a Federation vessel. If you truly think of me as but a mere 'pest', then I suppose the only way this encounter can end is in conflict." His ship's weapons come to life; yours soon do the same.</text>
				<ship hostile="true"/>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Continue...</text>
					<event load="COMBAT_CHECK"/>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>It's a glorious cause that will bring order and stability to the multiverse.</text>
			<event>
				<text>"Please. Do you really think I'm stupid enough to believe that's your honest answer? I think you're just lying to me hoping that I'll give you stuff. In that case, I see no need to prolong this conversation further." He cuts comms.</text>
			</event>
		</choice>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>It has potential, but was led astray by immoral methods.</text>
			<event>
				<text>"Finally, someone who understands me!" The rebel smiles before sighing despondently. "I joined the Rebellion because I thought it was a heroic organization aiming to 'shape the galaxy for the better'. Turns out it's far less noble than the commercials made it out to be. No care or respect for basic rights, constant infighting between different corps, the entirety of upper management being completely useless... you get the idea. At this point, I've got half a mind to quit and find work at a factory somewhere, but the rest of my family needs the money..."</text>
				<choice>
					<text>Why not join our ship? The pay's good, and we even get free healthcare insurance.</text>
					<event>
						<text>"Sure, I guess. At least I won't have to listen to my commander bark orders at me anymore."</text>
						<crewMember class="human_soldier">Fred</crewMember>
					</event>
				</choice>
				<choice>
					<text>What about forming a reform club? Try and spark change from within?</text>
					<event>
						<text>"That's an idea. Never thought I'd be taking advice from a Fed, but I'm desperate enough to try anything at this point." The rebel gives you some scrap as thanks before heading out.</text>
						<autoReward level="MED">scrap-only</autoReward>
					</event>
				</choice>
			</event>
		</choice> 
	</event>

	<event name="DISTRESS_FRONTIER_FAKE_NEWS" distress="true" unique="true">
		<text>Instead of a distress signal, your comms are flooded with a barrage of ads encouraging enlistment in the MV Rebels. "Th-he Federation is a bunch of liver-eating sheep-brained cannon fodder! Aliens are scientifically less good than humans! Are YOU a Rebel tired of all the dumb, lazy xeno scum polluting our universe? Then join the Multiversal Corps and start slaughtering zoltan children TODAY! Call us at +1(416) 999-999..." The transmission keeps going.</text>
		<choice hidden="true">
			<text>Look around a bit.</text>
			<event>
				<text>With some difficulty, you manage to locate the source of the distress signal - a large Auto-Station flanked by a small Engineer vessel. The latter ship hails you, "A Renegade? What are you doing here?"</text>
				<choice hidden="true">
					<text>Inquire about the distress beacon.</text>
					<event>
						<text>"Oh right, THAT. Long story short, some random jerkwad thought it'd be funny to hack this here news station to make it more 'politically correct'. Now it's spewing misinformation and vitriol everywhere across all broadband channels for far longer than its speakers were designed to run for. I've been trying to shut it down to stop it from overheating for a while now, but nothing seems to work. My job's supposed to be hardware, not software!"</text>
						<choice hidden="true">
							<text>Can we help?</text>
							<event>
								<text>"Sure. If you happen to have something that can purge the virus remotely, that'd be great. Otherwise, you could try and send someone inside to disable it from within. One thing though - whatever you're planning on doing, make it quick. I'd wager we have around... 30 minutes or so before the entire thing melts down."</text>
								<choice hidden="true" req="hacking" lvl="3" blue="true">
									<text>(Advanced Hacking) Hack the station to purge the virus.</text>
									<event>
										<text>Your hacking system easily bypasses the station's firewalls and swiftly purges the virus from its systems. The Engineer is thankful for your assistance and gives you a drone as thanks.</text>
										<autoReward level="HIGH">drone</autoReward>
									</event>
								</choice>
								<choice hidden="true" req="ANTI_VIRUS" blue="true">
									<text>(Anti-Virus Module) Use your Antivirus to purge the virus.</text>
									<event>
										<text>You fire up the Anti-virus module and are able to remove the virus before it can cause too much damage. The Engineer thanks you and gives you a drone before leaving.</text>
										<autoReward level="MED">drone</autoReward>
									</event>	
								</choice>
								<choice hidden="true" req="human_engineer" blue="false">
									<text>Your engineer isn't qualified enough for this.</text>
									<event load="OPTION_INVALID"/>
								</choice>
								<choice>
									<text>We have nothing to proceed with.</text>
									<event>
										<text>You pilot your ship away from the Auto-station as its speakers begin to go up in smoke. Within minutes, it goes up in flames and turns into a hunk of molten metal. "Welp, there goes any hope of that promotion I guess."</text>
									</event>
								</choice>
							</event>
					</event>
				</choice>	
			</event>
		</choice>
	</event>
</FTL>